https://www.silicones.eu/privacy-centre/

Privacy Centre
CES is committed to protecting privacy of personal data. Our Privacy Centre provides information on how we collect, store and process personal data and allows visitors to exercise their rights in line with the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
Find out more on how we collect and process personal data
Cookies Policy
You can consult our cookies policy and a full list of cookies used on this website.
Cookies Policy
Privacy Policy
You can read our privacy policy that outlines how we collect, process and store data.
Privacy Policy
Terms of Use
Terms of use outline a range of policies and disclaimers specific to this site.
Terms of Use
Your Rights
The EU’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) grants you specific rights to find out more on the personal data we have, to be deleted from our databases, to correct data and to limit the processing of your personal data.
Right to information
Ask us if we hold any of your personal data and how it is processed and the rationale for the data processing.
Request Information
Right to access
Request a copy of the personal datawe have in our database.
Request Information
Right to rectification
If you think the personal data we have on record is not up to date or incorrect, you can ask us to correct it.
Request Information
Right to withdraw consent
If you would like to withdraw a previously given consent to store your personal data or send you information you can withdraw that consent.
Withdraw Consent
Right to object
If you would like us to keep your personal data on record but no longer process this data (e.g. send you newsletters), please be specific as to what type of processing you object to.
Send a Request
Right to object to automated processing
We do not process personal data automatically.
Right of Erasure
If you would like to be deleted from our database as far as it is in line with other applicable laws you click on the button below.
Send a Request
Right for data portability
If you would like your personal data to be transferred to another organisation, we will provide your data in a machine readable format.
Send a Request
Questions?
If anything is unclear, please
Contact Us
Important
For all requests, please include your full name and e-mail address which will help us in their handling.
If you have a complaint about our use of your information, you can contact the Belgian Privacy Commission.
Belgian Privacy Commission Drukpersstraat 35, 1000 Brussels Tel +32 (0)2 274 48 00
commission@privacycommission.be
CookiesTo make this site work properly, we sometimes place small data files called cookies on your device. Most big websites do this too.		Read more
Accept
Change Settings
Cookie Box Settings
Cookie Box Settings
Privacy settings
Decide which cookies you want to allow.
You can change these settings at any time. However, this can result in some functions no longer being available. For information on deleting the cookies, please consult your browser’s help function.
Learn more about the cookies we use.
With the slider, you can enable or disable different types of cookies:
Block all
Essentials
Functionality
Analytics
Advertising
This website will:
Essential: Remember your cookie permission settingEssential: Allow session cookiesEssential: Gather information you input into a contact forms, newsletter and other forms across all pagesEssential: Keep track of what you input in a shopping cartEssential: Authenticate that you are logged into your user accountEssential: Remember language version you selected
This website won't:
Remember your login detailsFunctionality: Remember social media settingsFunctionality: Remember selected region and countryAnalytics: Keep track of your visited pages and interaction takenAnalytics: Keep track about your location and region based on your IP numberAnalytics: Keep track of the time spent on each pageAnalytics: Increase the data quality of the statistics functionsAdvertising: Tailor information and advertising to your interests based on e.g. the content you have visited before. (Currently we do not use targeting or targeting cookies.Advertising: Gather personally identifiable information such as name and location
This website will:
Essential: Remember your cookie permission settingEssential: Allow session cookiesEssential: Gather information you input into a contact forms, newsletter and other forms across all pagesEssential: Keep track of what you input in a shopping cartEssential: Authenticate that you are logged into your user accountEssential: Remember language version you selectedFunctionality: Remember social media settingsFunctionality: Remember selected region and country
This website won't:
Remember your login detailsAnalytics: Keep track of your visited pages and interaction takenAnalytics: Keep track about your location and region based on your IP numberAnalytics: Keep track of the time spent on each pageAnalytics: Increase the data quality of the statistics functionsAdvertising: Tailor information and advertising to your interests based on e.g. the content you have visited before. (Currently we do not use targeting or targeting cookies.Advertising: Gather personally identifiable information such as name and location
This website will:
Essential: Remember your cookie permission settingEssential: Allow session cookiesEssential: Gather information you input into a contact forms, newsletter and other forms across all pagesEssential: Keep track of what you input in a shopping cartEssential: Authenticate that you are logged into your user accountEssential: Remember language version you selectedFunctionality: Remember social media settingsl Functionality: Remember selected region and countryAnalytics: Keep track of your visited pages and interaction takenAnalytics: Keep track about your location and region based on your IP numberAnalytics: Keep track of the time spent on each pageAnalytics: Increase the data quality of the statistics functions
This website won't:
Remember your login detailsAdvertising: Use information for tailored advertising with third partiesAdvertising: Allow you to connect to social sitesAdvertising: Identify device you are usingAdvertising: Gather personally identifiable information such as name and location
This website will:
Essential: Remember your cookie permission settingEssential: Allow session cookiesEssential: Gather information you input into a contact forms, newsletter and other forms across all pagesEssential: Keep track of what you input in a shopping cartEssential: Authenticate that you are logged into your user accountEssential: Remember language version you selectedFunctionality: Remember social media settingsl Functionality: Remember selected region and countryAnalytics: Keep track of your visited pages and interaction takenAnalytics: Keep track about your location and region based on your IP numberAnalytics: Keep track of the time spent on each pageAnalytics: Increase the data quality of the statistics functionsAdvertising: Use information for tailored advertising with third partiesAdvertising: Allow you to connect to social sitesl Advertising: Identify device you are usingAdvertising: Gather personally identifiable information such as name and location
This website won't:
Remember your login details
Save & Close
